[{"question": " so who\u0092s idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?", "answer": " oh, some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh my god, they took my idea!", "answer": " that was you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh my god, are you guys okay?", "answer": " are you all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey. y'know with that goatee you kinda look like satan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " oh, so that\u0092s why the priest threw holy water on me.  okay, listen, you have to cheer up! okay? you should come out with ross and me, i mean anything is better than sitting around here crying all day about kate.", "answer": " hey i was crying because, because nobody believed quincy\u0092s theory. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  i\u0092m gonna be on tv!!", "answer": " no way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yeah! they\u0092re putting together this panel to talk about these fossils they just found in peru and the discovery channel\u0092s gonna film it!", "answer": " oh my god! who\u0092s gonna watch that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " thanks. you ready to go?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " saw a girl with that vest.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  while most of us think of chocolate bunnies and baskets as traditional easter gifts. some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.  unfortunately, the sad fact remains that most of these little guys won\u0092t live to see the fourth of july.  because of as a result of improper care, they will be dead.", "answer": "  yeah, hi. you guys got any of those baby chicks? \u0091cause i was watching this ah, commercial on tv and man, those guys are cute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi! hey, pete you\u0092re back! hey, check this out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " wow! you\u0092re a lot sturdier that chandler. he crumpled like a piece of paper. so how was you\u0092re trip?", "answer": " well...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh, what\u0092d ya bring me?!  awww, hotel toiletries from japan. oh, these are gonna go in my permanent collection. you want some coffee?", "answer": " yeah, sure, that\u0092d be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  regular or decaf?", "answer": " ah, which ever is closest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " so ask me what i did today.", "answer": " so what did you do today pete?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i bought a restaurant and i would like you to be the head chef.", "answer": " what?! oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " can you believe he just offered me a restaurant?", "answer": " what a jerk! you want me to kick his ass?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i mean this has been like my dream since i got my first easy bake oven and opened easy monica\u0092s bakery. i mean i would kill for this job. i mean i can totally do this job, and god knows i paid my dues.  but pete\u0092s just doing this because he has a crush on me.", "answer": " and you\u0092re still not attracted to him at all?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hmm, no. i mean how can i accept a restaurant from him? i-i-i-i can\u0092t. i couldn\u0092t even accept a necklace from stu vincent in the seventh grade.", "answer": " yeah, but mon that\u0092s totally different. he was you\u0092re health teacher.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " what? honey.", "answer": " oh, i am, my side still hurts from when you crashed into me yesterday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh god, i\u0092m so sorry.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " ow!!", "answer": " oh god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  hey, you guys! guess what?", "answer": "  got a job on a river boat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " y'know what i didn\u0092t wear this suit for a year because you hated it. well, guess what? you\u0092re not my girlfriend anymore so...", "answer": " oh i see, so this suit is making a point.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " right.", "answer": " now that you\u0092re on you\u0092re own, you\u0092re free to look as stupid as you like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  you like it right?", "answer": " oh absolutely. i like it even more on you than i did on colonel sanders.  ross! ross! i\u0092m kidding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " yeah, come here!", "answer": " what-what was it you were gonna tell us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah. oh! was how you invented the cotton gin?!", "answer": " okay, good bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " so um, after you put the suggestion in the box, how long did it take for the roller skating thing to happen.", "answer": " umm, oh, about three months.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, so i guess that\u0092s about ah, two weeks before the topless thing kicks in.", "answer": "  hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " i got you something! open it! open it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " okay.  it\u0092s a chicken.", "answer": " it\u0092s cute, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa, you guys, do you know anything about chicks?", "answer": " fowl? no. women? nooo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " okay, well they are a huge responsibility, especially at this age. they require constant care. they-they need just the right food, and lot\u0092s and lot\u0092s of love.", "answer": " oh, well no problem there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " so? i mean have you thought about it?", "answer": " okay. here\u0092s the thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh no, not the thing. i hate the thing. what\u0092s the thing?", "answer": " i can\u0092t do it. i\u0092m sorry, i wish i could, but umm, see you have these feelings for me....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " wait, wait, wait, wait, that\u0092s-that\u0092s what you\u0092re worried about? if that\u0092s the problem, we\u0092ve got no problem.", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no! look, i was gonna tell you this over dinner, but i met somebody else. on my trip.", "answer": " oh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " her name\u0092s ann, she\u0092s a journalist. ahh, we met on the plane. she asked me if she could finish off my peanuts, i thought she said something else, we had a big laugh. yeah, i just, i mean i got, i got tired of waiting.", "answer": " oh, that\u0092s great! i mean i\u0092m-i\u0092m sorry, but i\u0092m so happy for you. and now i can work for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " i guess you can.", "answer": " oh my god! oh, this is incredible! ohh!  all right, y'know what? i\u0092m just gonna roll right into that office and-and quit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " okay.  can you give me a little push?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah, sure. good luck!", "answer": "  i\u0092m quitting!! woo-hoo!  i\u0092m okay!! i\u0092m all right!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  wow! that\u0092s exciting, you went to japan, made up a woman.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i\u0092m just saying, this woman, i mean she\u0092s fictitious. no?", "answer": " why would you say that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " \u0091cause you\u0092re still into monica. so you told her there was somebody else so she would agree to work with you, so \u0091cause you figure oh if you spent a lot of time together, maybe something might happen, and...", "answer": " you\u0092re good. you\u0092re good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " yeah, no, i\u0092m fairly intuitive and psychic. it\u0092s a substantial gift.", "answer": " listen, can you promise me that you won\u0092t tell her though?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " absolutely, oh i promise. tell her what?", "answer": " thanks a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " okay, but this is the last time.  with a chick-chick here, and a chick-chick there. here a chick, there a chick, everywhere a chick-chick--chickeeeen.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " how\u0092s she doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " she?", "answer": " well yeah, don\u0092t-don\u0092t you think it\u0092s a she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know.  i can\u0092t tell, what ever it was went back in too quickly.", "answer": " well, anyway, i got to go change, i\u0092m ah, meeting some of the cast for drinks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i stayed home from work today while you were at rehearsal so somebody could be here with our chick!", "answer": " hey! who was up from 2 o\u0092clock this morning until 5 o\u0092clock this morning trying to get her back to sleep?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " you don\u0092t think i get up when you get up?", "answer": " ohhh, here it comes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " yes, here it comes! i\u0092m stuck here all day, and then you come in and spend two seconds with us and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends? well i don\u0092t think so mister!", "answer": " hey!! i need to relax! okay? i was working all day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " and you don\u0092t think taking care of our chick is work?", "answer": " that\u0092s not what i said. okay, i just meant...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i know what you meant!!  you notice that ever since we got this chick, we\u0092ve been fighting a lot more than we used too?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, maybe we weren\u0092t ready to have a chick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i\u0092ll take her back tomorrow.", "answer": " do you think we\u0092ll get our three bucks back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  ohhh, hey! all right, listen, i-i have that tv thing in like two hours, and i need your help, okay? what do you think?  this blue suit, or this brown one?", "answer": " well, the brown one brings out your eyes, but your butt looks great in the blue one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " wow! that aspirin dance really works!", "answer": "  oww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh my god, is that still...", "answer": " i\u0092m fine, i\u0092m fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no you\u0092re not.", "answer": " yes i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " rach!", "answer": " look, i\u0092m fine. watch.  look at that.  whoa-whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  okay, okay. look, you have got to go to a doctor! okay?", "answer": " no. i have got to get ready and go to a dinner at my bosses house. it\u0092s a very big deal, there\u0092s a lot of people there i have to meet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " and i\u0092m sure you\u0092re gonna make a big impression. hi! i\u0092m rachel green. it\u0092s nice to meet you.  come on, you probably have a broken rib!", "answer": " well, i will go to the hospital tomorrow, it\u0092ll still be broken then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " rach...", "answer": " but y'know, i could use a hand getting ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " rachel...", "answer": " look, either help me or go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " fine. i\u0092ll go.", "answer": "  okay, but before you go, could you help me first?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  sure. i\u0092ll help you.", "answer": "  oh, good! good! do you guys know how to get a chick out of a vcr?! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  y'know what? i cannot do this with my left hand! would you please, help me with this too?", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay. this stuff?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " careful. light. okay, do you know how, just sweep it across the lid. okay? just sweep it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh-ho!", "answer": " sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey! that\u0092s just poking me in the eye!", "answer": " sorry, i\u0092m sorry. close, close, close...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " okay, just sweep it.", "answer": " i\u0092m sweeping...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " right.", "answer": " sweep, sweep....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " okay, now make it even, \u0091cause we don\u0092t...", "answer": " what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " no. no, y'know you don\u0092t, you don\u0092t wear enough of this.  what?", "answer": " since when, since when do you think i don\u0092t wear enough of this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " blow it.", "answer": "  sorry. \u0091cause umm, i think this will make you a little more sophisticated.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hey, guess what i\u0092m doing tonight.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " i\u0092m checking out the restaurant with pete.", "answer": " ohh, monica, i am so excited for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " ooh, i have to tell you something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " but i can\u0092t tell you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " okay, but wouldn\u0092t it be easier if you had to tell me something that you could tell me.", "answer": " well, sure in a perfect world. but, no, i promised i wouldn\u0092t tell, and i swore to like all my gods.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " okay. does it have to do with ross and rachel?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " does it have to do with joey?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " does it have to do with-with chandler and that sock that he keeps by his bed?", "answer": " no, but let\u0092s come back to that later!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " yep?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " sure, i\u0092ll just sit next to the trans-sexual from purchasing.", "answer": " okay, come on! all right, i gotta go! so good luck at the party. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh wait, ross, would you just stay and help me get dressed?", "answer": "  sure, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " okay. okay, great! umm, okay, just turn around.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i don\u0092t want you to see me naked!", "answer": " rachel, i\u0092ve seen you naked a million times. i ate hot fudge off you naked. remember, i-i sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your belly button?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yeah, but that was different. y\u0092know? i mean, we were, we were going out then, now i think it\u0092s weird.", "answer": " rach, y'know i can see you naked any time i want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " all i have to do is close my eyes. see?  woo-hoo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " ross! stop that!", "answer": " ah, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " come on! i don\u0092t want you thinking of me like that any more!", "answer": " ahh, sorry, nothing you can do about it. it\u0092s one of my ah, rights as the ex-boyfriend.  oop, oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " stop it! cut it out! cut it out!", "answer": " okay, okay, i\u0092m sorry, it will never happen...  uh-oh! wait a minute! wait-wait, now there are a hundred of you and i\u0092m the king.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " rosss...", "answer": " come on, would you grow up? it\u0092s no big deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " all right.  fine.", "answer": " yowzah!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " o-kay!! see what you did, i\u0092m gonna be doing it by myself now. okay?", "answer": " aww, come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " that\u0092s it.  ow!!!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh-ow!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " look...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " ow! ow!", "answer": " easy. easy. you have to go to the hospital. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay, i do.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i really do.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092m gonna get your coat and then i\u0092ll-i\u0092ll put you in a cab.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " okay. oh wait, wait-wait, you\u0092re not gonna come with me?", "answer": "  of course i am. i just have to make a call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " thank you.  oww!!!! god!", "answer": "  what?! i wh-, what\u0092s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " does it involve travel?", "answer": " noo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " does it involve clogs?", "answer": " oh, wait, wait. clogs, or claws?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " clogs.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " claws?!", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " okay, so it doesn\u0092t involve ross or rachel or chandler or joey. but, what about pete?", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what is it?! what about pete?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " okay, i feel like i\u0092m talking to lassie. all right, phoebe would you just tell me!", "answer": " i can\u0092t!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i, but you\u0092re so close! no!", "answer": " okay, does it involve something to do with pete\u0092s computer company?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i know. see, yes. that\u0092s yasmine bleeth, she\u0092s a completely different kind of chick. i love you both. but in very different ways.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  ohhh.  ahh! what are you doing?! i thought you were gonna take her back to the store today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " if they can\u0092t find a home for her, they kill her! and i\u0092m not gonna let that happen to little yasmine!", "answer": " okay, good, good, good, \u0091cause, good, \u0091cause i was kinda having second thoughts too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " okay. and it\u0092s not just chicks y'know? it\u0092s all kinds of other animals!", "answer": " that\u0092s horrible! well, you did the right thing man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " i don\u0092t believe this! wow, look at this refridgerator! it\u0092s gigantic! i mean i could live in this thing! i\u0092d be cold, but i\u0092m always cold. oh my god, look at these spider burners! i love spider burners.", "answer": " so you like it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " did you just smell my hair?", "answer": " nooo. uh-huh, no way. what? no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " oh god.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " you still have feelings for me don\u0092t you?", "answer": " now, nooo! i\u0092m just excited about the restaurant, that\u0092s all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " pete.", "answer": " okay, i love you. is that so bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s not bad. it\u0092s not bad at all. it\u0092s-it\u0092s really nice.", "answer": " look, the only who stands to get hurt is me. and i\u0092m okay with that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " you may be okay about getting hurt, but i am not okay with being the one who hurts you. that\u0092s why i can\u0092t take this job.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " and well, we probably shouldn\u0092t see each other anymore. i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " okay, yeah. i mean... if that\u0092s, if that\u0092s really what you want, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry things didn\u0092t work out...", "answer": " all right shut up for a second and let me just see something.  oh, wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " okay, you\u0092d tell me the truth. right?", "answer": " rach, you can\u0092t look fat in an x-ray.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " okay! now you stay out here, and you think about what you did!!", "answer": "  that\u0092s a duck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " that\u0092s a bad duck!!!  how\u0092d the thing go tonight, ross?", "answer": " oh, it was, nah, well....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " what thing? what thing?", "answer": " nothing, ah there was this thing at the museum. come on.  easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " what thing? what is this thing?", "answer": " i was kinda, supposed to be on tv tonight for the discovery channel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " ross, why didn\u0092t you tell me that?", "answer": " eh, \u0091cause i knew that if i told you, you\u0092d make me go, and i knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. come on. come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " i cannot believe you.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": "  you should get some sleep.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": " so, i\u0092ll umm...", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m sorry i spoiled you\u0092re evening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " no, that\u0092s, no, as long as you\u0092re okay. so i\u0092ll ah, i\u0092ll see you tomorrow.", "answer": " um-hmm, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": " what \u0091cha doing?", "answer": " having a swim.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 353, "asentId": 354}, {"question": " what about the chick?", "answer": " chicks don\u0092t swim.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know. should we try it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": "  wait. give him a minute.", "answer": " noo!  oh, it\u0092s okay, it\u0092s okay, baby, baby, baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}]